Zach Kozac

Graphic Designer, Art Director, Illustrator

I've been designing for 9+ years and worked cross-functionally with folks from every department of a growing organization. I've had the opportunity to develop my skills in SaaS, Boutique and larger shops alike. I've established design as a part of company culture and laid down style-guide frameworks that can be used by any member of an organization. I'm a process-driven thinker who approaches design as a problem solver for the user, first and always.



EXPERIENCE

RJMetrics | 2012 - Present Lead Graphic Designer

As the first designer at RJM, I was the go-to resource for all things brand and design. I had the opportunity to work directly with the founders, as well as leaders from every arm of the organization as we grew from 18 to 140 employees. I crafted our logo/brand style-guide, helped develop our ever-evolving marketing message, and designed for both our marketing and product efforts.

Key Achievments:

- · Company Rebrand
- Style guide foundation
- Product UI/Chrome Upgrade
- 1st Customer Video Testimonial
- Office/Environment Design
- 2+ years of Marketing Strategy
- Conference & Event Collateral

• Devnuts & Jarvus Innovations | 2010 - 2012

Creative Director

Devnuts was a co-working space that brought freelancers together in hopes of getting better work for all. Jarvus, a service-based web-based application and SaaS boutique born from Devnut's mix of talents. I designed each identity and worked on all client project with a design component. This included designing everything from sketched interactions, to interactive wireframes, to responsive web mockups.

Key Achievments:

- Branding/Identity
- Style guide foundation
- Creative Direction/Management
- Office/Environment Design
- Working directly with Clients such as Penn, TEDxPhilly, and The Roots

Sevens and Sixes LLC | 2007 - 2009 Founder, Creative Director, Account Manager

I had worked up a fair amount of freelance clients, all getting some variation of identity, print, and/or web collateral. I linked up with a developer I had done work with who had a client roster of his own. I was responsible for design and client communication, and was a one-man content team for most of the company's duration. The experience was invaluable in regards to design/ development processes, client management, and business best practices.

Key Achievments:

Inception/Branding

- Branding/Marketing Consulting
- Client Acquisition and Managment
- Interactive Design

EXPERTISE

Branding, Creative Direction, Web Design, UX/UI, Copywriting,
Print Design, Marketing Strategy, Interior Design

MY SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, HTML/CSS (SASS),
Github, Microsoft Suite, Google Apps, Balsamiq, Omni

EDUCATION

Temple University

BA in Advertising Design | Class of 2007

LOOK ME UP

Recent Work | zachkozac.com

LinkedIn | linkedin.com/in/zach-kozac-9204026

Email | zach@zachkozac.com

Phone | 215.715.6782

Dribbble | dribbble.com/Zkozilla